It feels so good.
好舒服
What's this?
這是什麼？
Breast pads.
就是胸墊啊
They're magical items that make your boobs look bigger.
是塞進來就能讓胸部變大的神奇道具
Come on. You got two more.
來吧，還可以再揉兩次！
Okay. Last touch.
好，剩最後一次！
Okay. That's it. The fun's over.
好了，結束，到此結束！
Good, isn't it?
如何？揉起來是不是還不錯啊？
Congratulations on getting to touch nice boobs.
恭喜你揉到好胸部
Now we're even.
這樣就互不相欠了
Meowy is alive and kicking.
因為你救了喵子
-I don't have to be a Devil Hunter anymore -There's a lot I want to say…
-老子已經沒必要當惡魔獵人了 -雖然有很多話想說…
-but Makima would never let me go. -It's weird.
-可是卻逃不出真紀真的手掌心 -奇怪
I'll be so good as to assist you.
老子會好心協助你們的工作
Hope we can be good teammates.
再次請你多多指教啦
Meowy, time for bed.
喵子，該睡囉
Is that it?
就只有這樣？
CHAINSAW MAN
鏈鋸人
This is delicious.
這個真好吃
I want another plate.
老子還想再來一盤
-Give me that if you don't want it. -Hey you!
-不吃就給老子！ -妳這傢伙！
Where are we going to kill Devils today?
今天要去哪裡殺惡魔？
Hey.
喂
Chop!
手刀！
This is an apology for damaging buildings.
這是損壞建築的悔過書
This is a confirmation of the usage of the Devil's corpse.
這是確認惡魔屍體用途的文件
And…
然後這是國土交通省給的
Sign here, and here.
這份要在這兩處蓋章
Is all this paperwork annoying?
要處理一堆書面文件很討厭吧？
You defeated Bat Devil,
你明明打倒了蝙蝠惡魔 卻像是做了壞事
Denji, is there anything on your mind?
淀治，你是不是有什麼煩惱？
I…
我…
I finally got what I've always wanted.
我終於抓住了一直在追尋的東西
But it didn't feel that great
可是當我抓住了 那個東西卻沒有我想得那麼不得了
If I want something else in the future, when I finally get what I want,
假設未來我又去追逐 不同東西，緊握在手上時
would I still feel like I'm happier during the process?
會不會反倒覺得追逐的過程更幸福？
Then it's just a load of crap, isn't it?
那樣不就爛透了嗎？
What are you referring to?
你在講什麼事呢？
I touched a girl's boobs for the first time.
我第一次揉別人的胸部 結果卻不怎麼樣
Denji.
淀治
I think, for something like that,
我認為色色的事情
the more you know the other person,
越是了解對方就會越舒服
It's hard to tell what they're thinking.
因為要理解對方心裡的想法 是一件很困難的事
So you have to look carefully at their hands first.
一開始先試著仔細觀察對方的手
The length of their fingers.
手指大概多長？
Are their palms cold
手掌是冰的嗎？
or warm?
還是很溫暖？
The shape of their ears.
耳朵是怎樣的形狀？
Did anyone bite your finger before?
有沒有被人咬過手指？
B-Bite…
咬…
Remember this.
要記住喔
Even if you couldn't see,
即使你變得看不見
you have to be able to tell it's me
也要從我咬下去的力道判斷是我咬的
Remember.
你可要好好記住喔
I will.
我記住了
Denji.
淀治
I have a request.
我有事想拜託你
Is that okay?
可以嗎？
Yeah.
可以
I want you to defeat the Gun Devil.
希望你能打倒鎗之惡魔
The Gun Devil…
鎗之惡魔？
It showed up in America 13 years ago.
13年前出現在美國
Current whereabouts are unknown.
目前不知去向
Every Devil Hunter dreams to kill it.
是所有惡魔獵人都想殺死的對象
It's very strong.
那惡魔實力非常強
But I think you can kill it.
我認為你有本事殺死那個惡魔
Because you are more special than other Devil Hunters.
因為你比其他惡魔獵人都來得特別
If you can kill the Gun Devil,
假如你能殺死鎗之惡魔
I'll grant you a wish.
我就實現你一個願望 什麼願望都可以
If I can kill the Gun Devil…
如果我能殺死鎗之惡魔
Ms. Makima will grant me a wish.
真紀真小姐就會實現我一個願望 什麼願望都可以？
So… You mean…
所以意思是…
As long as I kill the Gun Devil,
只要我殺死鎗之惡魔
you'll do anything I want?
真紀真小姐就會實現 我的任何願望嗎？
Anything… Such as--
任何願望…
Cool. Even dirty stuff?
酷斃了，做那檔事也可以囉？
This mission is hard enough for me to believe that you'd deserve it.
因為是足以讓你如願做那檔事的 強大又邪惡的惡魔
It was when the whole world tried to use guns to gain an advantage over Devils.
作為對付惡魔的手段 有段時期全世界都想靠槍枝獲益
Guns started to get used in civil conflicts.
使用槍枝的案件與內戰隨之增加
Such cases were all over the news,
媒體也不斷報導這一類的新聞
which made the people even more afraid of guns.
人們變得比以前更害怕槍枝
There was a massive terrorist attack with guns involved in America.
美國出現了使用槍枝的大型恐攻
That was when the Gun Devil appeared.
在那天，鎗之惡魔現身了
"This is where I live."
“‘這就是我住的地方’
The City Mouse said.
城市老鼠這麼說”
"That house is so big."
“那棟房子居然這麼大
-"The City Mouse's family…" -Dad.
-城市老鼠的家人…” -爸爸
Let's go play catch.
我們去外面玩傳接球吧
Taiyo doesn't feel well.
大洋的身體不舒服
Go play by yourself.
你去玩能一個人玩的遊戲吧
Taiyo is always like that.
大洋平常就是這樣吧
He's sick all the time.
他根本沒有身體健康的時候
Big Brother should care for his sibling. Go and play alone.
你是哥哥所以要忍耐，自己去玩吧
I…
我…
I want to play with my big brother.
我想跟哥哥玩
Don't follow me.
不要跟著我
You're so annoying. Don't follow me.
煩死了，不要跟上來！
I want to play alone.
我可以自己一個人玩
Take that!
看我的！
Idiot. I told you to stop.
笨蛋，就叫你別丟了！
So cold.
好冰
Mom and Dad will kill me if you catch a cold.
要是你感冒，我一定會挨罵
Let's play catch so our hands won't get cold.
玩傳接球的話手就不會變冰了
Go home and get your gloves.
你回家拿手套來
Yeah!
好耶！
Gun Devil killed 1.2 million people in five minutes
約五分鐘內殺死120萬人後
and has been staying under the radar till now.
鎗之惡魔至今依舊銷聲匿跡
From then on, their fear of Devils grew stronger.
從那天起大家更加懼怕惡魔這種存在
The Devils got stronger than ever.
所有惡魔的力量都變得比以前更強
To keep the Gun Devil's strength under control as best as we could,
為了盡可能削弱鎗之惡魔的力量
the law forbids people to keep guns.
各地基本上都嚴禁持槍
The government started to limit the news reports of such cases too.
也開始限制案件與災害的報導
I see.
是喔，雖然我聽不太懂
but the gist is that it's unbelievably strong, right?
總之是個強得莫名其妙的傢伙吧？
Do you think you can defeat it?
你覺得自己能打倒那個惡魔嗎？
Well, I guess…
該怎麼說呢？
If I try my very best,
只要我豁出去，好好努力的話
there should be no problem.
就不會有問題吧
Then our first step
那首先第一步，要找出鎗之惡魔才行
How do we do that?
要怎麼找到那傢伙？
Here are the pieces of the Gun Devil that we've managed to collect.
這是目前收集的鎗之惡魔的肉片
It moves at a very high speed
好像是因為移動速度飛快 導致有部分身體燒焦脫落
When a Devil eats this,
不管是什麼惡魔
it'll get stronger because of the Gun Devil's power.
只要吃了這肉片 就會因為鎗之惡魔的力量變強
See? It stuck back together.
你看，黏在一起了
so that's why when a piece of his body reaches a certain size,
只要這些肉片變成一定程度的大小
it goes back to the original body.
好像就會主動回到本來的身體
When this piece gets bigger…
所以只要我們讓這塊肉片變得更大
we'll find the Gun Devil.
就能抵達鎗之惡魔的所在地
Found it.
找到了
This Devil ate a piece of the Gun Devil?
果然是吃了槍那傢伙的肉片嗎？
It is indeed too much for a low-level Devil.
以雜碎惡魔而言，確實強過頭了
Whichever happened, it doesn't change our mission.
不論是哪個，我們要做的事都一樣
We kill every Devil there is.
殺光惡魔
Then we can find it.
然後就能找到那傢伙
The Public Safety Sector got a mission.
公安收到驅除惡魔的委託
Someone saw a Devil in a hotel.
有人在旅館內部目擊到惡魔
The guests' status is unknown.
旅館住客生死不明
Several civil Devil Hunters died trying to kill this Devil.
數名民間惡魔獵人 在驅除惡魔的過程中身亡
It probably ate a piece of the Gun Devil.
那個惡魔恐怕吃了鎗之惡魔的肉片
Tokyo Special Division 4
公安對魔特異四課派遣六人出動
The Devil is hiding somewhere in the hotel.
惡魔就潛伏在這棟旅館裡某處
It's not a regular Devil.
而且不是普通的惡魔
It's probably a Devil who ate a piece of the Gun Devil.
是吃了鎗之惡魔肉片的惡魔
It can probably be Gun Devil itself.
搞不好是鎗之惡魔本尊啊
The bigger the piece, the stronger the attraction.
肉片越大，吸引力越強
It can't be the Gun Devil.
這種程度的話不是
Sounds great.
那東西真不錯，把它給老子
You forgot about honorifics.
你們忘了要用敬語嗎？
-Huh?
-什麼？
-Why? What do we get out of it? -Humans are so stupid and arrogant.
-又沒好處，幹嘛對你用敬語？ -人類愚蠢又傲慢！
Mr. Hayakawa.
早川前輩
Sir.
前輩
Good.
及格
Yeah!
好耶
-That's easy. -Mr. Hayakawa.
-這傢伙真好搞定 -早川前輩
Should we really trust them as our comrades
作為今後一同對抗惡魔的戰友
when battling the Devils?
將背後交給那些傢伙沒問題嗎？
A Fiend and a rascal.
一個是魔人，一個是小混混
I can't trust them.
我無法信任他們
You don't have to.
不必將背後交給他們
They are the first to face Devils in missions.
驅除惡魔基本上是叫這兩人先攻
If they try to run away or betray us,
要是他們逃走或向惡魔倒戈時
we can just kill them.
那我們就殺死他們
Darn, that's how you treat animals.
那是對待畜生的方式吧
Why is he so grumpy?
這傢伙超火大的耶
Is it because of this morning?
是因為早上那個吧？
Did that prank go too far?
那個惡作劇玩過頭了嗎？
That wasn't a prank anymore.
那程度已經超過惡作劇了 宰了你們喔！
Wow, scary. What happened?
好可怕，到底是怎麼了？
Aki, don't go so hard on these poor kids.
阿秋，只會嚴格管教的話 他們太可憐了
That's right.
就是啊
I almost got killed by Bat and I don't even get to rest.
我之前差點被蝙蝠殺掉 現在緊接著就要工作
I want a reward.
給我獎勵
Right. I'll be so good as to offer something.
好，那我就來助一臂之力
Whoever kills the Devil this time,
這次打倒惡魔的人
I'll kiss them on the cheeks.
我會親他的臉頰
No. Please don't do that.
不行，請妳別做那種事
How could a maiden…
還沒出嫁的少女做那種不檢點的事…
Motivation only comes with reward.
有獎勵大家才會有幹勁啊
Right?
對吧？
I don't need a kiss.
我也不需要親親
Don't worry. I have my motivation.
放心吧，我有幹勁
What's this?
奇怪
I've decided who I'm gonna kiss.
我已經決定初吻的對象了
I'll collect whatever pieces just for her.
為了那個人，我會收集那個什麼肉片
I won't kiss anyone before I kill the Gun Devil.
直到殺死鎗之惡魔之前，我不會接吻
Oh, my.
真意外，竟然當著阿秋的面說這種話
And someone gave me an important lesson.
而且有人教我一件重要的事
Those things only feel good when you understand each other.
要互相理解對方 做色色的事才會舒服
I don't even know your name, so of course, I'm not interested in your kiss.
我連妳叫什麼都不知道 對妳的嘴唇當然沒興趣
Really now?
是喔
Well Denji, if you kill the Devil,
那麼，如果你打倒了惡魔
I'll give you a French kiss.
我就給你舌吻
Hey! Stop!
喂，站住！
It's dangerous to act alone. Don't run!
單獨行動很危險，停下來！
8TH FLOOR
（八樓）
-It's so fun to tease boys. -Did you hear…
-戲弄男生最有趣了 -你有沒有聽到？
What should I do…
怎麼辦？
I want to drink blood.
老子想喝血
It's dangerous! I told you to stop!
這樣很危險，我不是叫你停下來嗎？
For the last six months,
這半年以來 是姬野前輩鍛鍊我、照顧我
How can a nameless rascal take her lips?
與其被來路不明的小混混 奪走她的嘴唇
I'd rather get a kiss on the cheek.
不如由我收下臉頰的吻！
Piss off!
滾開
Get away from me, stinky guy! Gross!
臭男人不要貼上來，有夠噁心
Are you kidding? You're just a rookie…
開什麼玩笑，你這個剛加入的新人…
-Ms. Himeno. -Why would I care?
-姬野前輩 -關我什麼事？
-Can we use these rookies? -Come on!
-新人們派得上用場嗎？ -來吧，再來啊！
Arai is not strong enough, but he's motivated.
-荒井實力有待加強，不過幹勁十足 -給我認真點，想玩就滾回去
-Kobeni is not brave, but she's strong. -Go…
-上啊… -小紅個性畏縮，卻很能幹
Aki, do you think they can survive?
阿秋，你覺得 這四個新人能活下來嗎？
Let's kill each other!
互相殘殺啊？
It doesn't matter whether I think they are strong or not.
不論是我認為強的人或是不強的人
After a year, they'll all either die or quit.
只要待上一年不是死了就是回歸民間
-That's not what I asked. -I'll kill you, Power!
-這是答非所問 -帕瓦，我也要殺了妳
-Don't die, Aki. -I'll kill you too, short guy!
-阿秋，你別死喔 -小個子，連妳一起殺了
Why?
為什麼？
Himeno.
姬野
He's your new teammate.
他是妳的新搭檔
He's a little bratty, but good enough to use.
沒大沒小的 不過多少將他訓練成戰力了
Do work hard.
你們好好加油
I'm Aki.
我叫秋，請多指教
Can we use you?
你派得上用場嗎？
Probably. Who knows?
應該吧，天曉得
You're my sixth teammate.
你是我第六位搭檔
They all died.
其他人都死光了
They all died because they were all useless.
因為是廢物雜碎，全都死掉了
Don't die, Aki.
阿秋，你別死喔
There's not a sight of the Devil.
話說回來，到處都沒看見惡魔嘛
Can we trust that piece you have?
真的能相信你手上的肉片嗎？
I'm dozing off.
好想睡
Aki.
阿秋
It's coming.
要來了
Got you!
抓到了！
It's floating!
浮起來了？
Let's fight!
來戰鬥吧！
Dirty Devil.
臭惡魔被老子嚇得浮起來了！
No, that's my ability.
不是啦，那是我的能力
What?
什麼？
I made a contract with Ghost Devil.
我是跟幽靈惡魔立下了契約
I gave it my right eye to use its power.
讓惡魔吃了右眼，換來能力
I can control its right hand.
能夠使用幽靈的右手
My Ghost is invisible and strong. Isn't that convenient?
我的幽靈是透明的 力量又大，很方便吧？
How is it, Aki?
怎麼樣？阿秋
Is there a piece of Gun?
有槍那傢伙的肉片嗎？
No reaction.
沒有出現強烈反應
It's not this one.
不是這傢伙
Yeah?
是嗎？
Let's go upstairs then.
那去樓上看看吧
Is it okay for you to tell me all about your ability like that?
妳剛才那樣在老子面前 滔滔不絕講自己的能力沒問題嗎？
I thought you were here to keep me under control.
你們過來不是為了壓制老子嗎？
It's easier to work together if you know my ability.
知道能力比較好合作吧
And I've still got an ace up my sleeve. It's fine…
而且我還藏了殺手鐧，沒問題的啦
Really?
真的嗎？
What if I say I'll kill this girl?
那假如老子說要殺了這傢伙呢？
Put your weapon away.
把武器收起來
I can kill you anytime if you try something funny.
敢動歪腦筋，我隨時都能勒死妳
I can't touch it…
摸不到
Let's save all the trouble and be nice to each other.
為了省去麻煩，我們好好相處吧
One day I'll eat you!
總有一天老子會吃了妳
Don't you dare. She's gonna kill me.
她還要親我，不准吃
You lot. The Devil is around here.
你們幾個，惡魔還埋伏在附近
Be quiet…
安靜一點…
Eh?
奇怪
-Yeah? -Whatever, idiot.
-隨便妳怎麼說 -是啊
This is the 8th floor.
-這裡也是八樓耶 -要煮成什麼料理呢？
Maybe you saw it wrong?
是不是你看錯啦？
No. Something's wrong. I'll go check.
才不是！一定有問題，我去確認
Got it. I'll make it a steak.
想好了，煎成肉排吃掉吧
Steak?
肉排？
I want to try that.
我好想吃吃看肉排
Eh?
奇怪
Arai just went downstairs, right?
荒井剛才是走下樓沒錯吧？